{"sentence_id": "sent_000013", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 13, "text": "He was also fascinated by science and the natural world, but he was uninterested in other subjects.", "tokens": ["He", "was", "also", "fascinated", "by", "science", "and", "the", "natural", "world", ",", "but", "he", "was", "uninterested", "in", "other", "subjects", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 6], [7, 11], [12, 22], [23, 25], [26, 33], [34, 37], [38, 41], [42, 49], [50, 55], [55, 56], [57, 60], [61, 63], [64, 67], [68, 80], [81, 83], [84, 89], [90, 98], [98, 99]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000020", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 20, "text": "On 16 March 1935, he was elected a Fellow of King’s College, which allowed him to remain in Cambridge and continue his mathematical work.", "tokens": ["On", "16", "March", "1935", ",", "he", "was", "elected", "a", "Fellow", "of", "King", "’", "s", "College", ",", "which", "allowed", "him", "to", "remain", "in", "Cambridge", "and", "continue", "his", "mathematical", "work", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 5], [6, 11], [12, 16], [16, 17], [18, 20], [21, 24], [25, 32], [33, 34], [35, 41], [42, 44], [45, 49], [49, 50], [50, 51], [52, 59], [59, 60], [61, 66], [67, 74], [75, 78], [79, 81], [82, 88], [89, 91], [92, 101], [102, 105], [106, 114], [115, 118], [119, 131], [132, 136], [136, 137]], "normalized_time": ["1935-03-16"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "16 March 1935", "normalized": "1935-03-16", "type": "date", "offset_start": 3, "offset_end": 16}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-AWARD", "I-AWARD", "I-AWARD", "I-AWARD", "I-AWARD", "I-AWARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000030", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 30, "text": "three years at Princeton University.", "tokens": ["three", "years", "at", "Princeton", "University", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 5], [6, 11], [12, 14], [15, 24], [25, 35], [35, 36]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000040", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 40, "text": "He played rugby, hockey and golf at school, and when he went to Cambridge, he took up rowing – competing for King’s College in university competitions.", "tokens": ["He", "played", "rugby", ",", "hockey", "and", "golf", "at", "school", ",", "and", "when", "he", "went", "to", "Cambridge", ",", "he", "took", "up", "rowing", "–", "competing", "for", "King", "’", "s", "College", "in", "university", "competitions", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 9], [10, 15], [15, 16], [17, 23], [24, 27], [28, 32], [33, 35], [36, 42], [42, 43], [44, 47], [48, 52], [53, 55], [56, 60], [61, 63], [64, 73], [73, 74], [75, 77], [78, 82], [83, 85], [86, 92], [93, 94], [95, 104], [105, 108], [109, 113], [113, 114], [114, 115], [116, 123], [124, 126], [127, 137], [138, 150], [150, 151]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000047", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 47, "text": "In addition to his academic work, Alan Turing was a keen sportsman.", "tokens": ["In", "addition", "to", "his", "academic", "work", ",", "Alan", "Turing", "was", "a", "keen", "sportsman", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 11], [12, 14], [15, 18], [19, 27], [28, 32], [32, 33], [34, 38], [39, 45], [46, 49], [50, 51], [52, 56], [57, 66], [66, 67]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000054", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 54, "text": "The paper was mostly about whether all mathematics was provable by logical reasoning, a question most recently articulated by German mathematician David Hilbert in 1928.", "tokens": ["The", "paper", "was", "mostly", "about", "whether", "all", "mathematics", "was", "provable", "by", "logical", "reasoning", ",", "a", "question", "most", "recently", "articulated", "by", "German", "mathematician", "David", "Hilbert", "in", "1928", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 3], [4, 9], [10, 13], [14, 20], [21, 26], [27, 34], [35, 38], [39, 50], [51, 54], [55, 63], [64, 66], [67, 74], [75, 84], [84, 85], [86, 87], [88, 96], [97, 101], [102, 110], [111, 122], [123, 125], [126, 132], [133, 146], [147, 152], [153, 160], [161, 163], [164, 168], [168, 169]], "normalized_time": ["1928"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1928", "normalized": "1928", "type": "year", "offset_start": 164, "offset_end": 168}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000064", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 64, "text": "Turing helped to break Enigma In September 1939, Turing joined the Government Code and Cypher School (GC&CS) at Bletchley Park.", "tokens": ["Turing", "helped", "to", "break", "Enigma", "In", "September", "1939", ",", "Turing", "joined", "the", "Government", "Code", "and", "Cypher", "School", "(", "GC", "&", "CS", ")", "at", "Bletchley", "Park", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 6], [7, 13], [14, 16], [17, 22], [23, 29], [30, 32], [33, 42], [43, 47], [47, 48], [49, 55], [56, 62], [63, 66], [67, 77], [78, 82], [83, 86], [87, 93], [94, 100], [101, 102], [102, 104], [104, 105], [105, 107], [107, 108], [109, 111], [112, 121], [122, 126], [126, 127]], "normalized_time": ["1939-09"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "September 1939", "normalized": "1939-09", "type": "month_year", "offset_start": 33, "offset_end": 47}], "labels": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-MACHINE", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000070", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 70, "text": "An Enigma cipher machine.", "tokens": ["An", "Enigma", "cipher", "machine", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 9], [10, 16], [17, 24], [24, 25]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "B-MACHINE", "I-MACHINE", "I-MACHINE", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000101", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 101, "text": "However, in 1948, before ACE was completed, Turing moved to Manchester University, where he joined a team led by his former Bletchley Park colleague Max Newman, and was appointed as ‘Deputy Director of the Royal Society Computing Laboratory’.", "tokens": ["However", ",", "in", "1948", ",", "before", "ACE", "was", "completed", ",", "Turing", "moved", "to", "Manchester", "University", ",", "where", "he", "joined", "a", "team", "led", "by", "his", "former", "Bletchley", "Park", "colleague", "Max", "Newman", ",", "and", "was", "appointed", "as", "‘", "Deputy", "Director", "of", "the", "Royal", "Society", "Computing", "Laboratory", "’", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 7], [7, 8], [9, 11], [12, 16], [16, 17], [18, 24], [25, 28], [29, 32], [33, 42], [42, 43], [44, 50], [51, 56], [57, 59], [60, 70], [71, 81], [81, 82], [83, 88], [89, 91], [92, 98], [99, 100], [101, 105], [106, 109], [110, 112], [113, 116], [117, 123], [124, 133], [134, 138], [139, 148], [149, 152], [153, 159], [159, 160], [161, 164], [165, 168], [169, 178], [179, 181], [182, 183], [183, 189], [190, 198], [199, 201], [202, 205], [206, 211], [212, 219], [220, 229], [230, 240], [240, 241], [241, 242]], "normalized_time": ["1948"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1948", "normalized": "1948", "type": "year", "offset_start": 12, "offset_end": 16}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-MACHINE", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "label_source": "manual_reviewed_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked_manual_reviewed", "weak_label_confidence": 0.95, "weak_label_stage": "manual_reviewed"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000103", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 103, "text": "Turing worked on programming the computer and devised the first manual for its operation.", "tokens": ["Turing", "worked", "on", "programming", "the", "computer", "and", "devised", "the", "first", "manual", "for", "its", "operation", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 6], [7, 13], [14, 16], [17, 28], [29, 32], [33, 41], [42, 45], [46, 53], [54, 57], [58, 63], [64, 70], [71, 74], [75, 78], [79, 88], [88, 89]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000105", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 105, "text": "Turing pioneered the idea of Artificial Intelligence In the 1950s, Turing continued to theorise about the potential of computers in the future.", "tokens": ["Turing", "pioneered", "the", "idea", "of", "Artificial", "Intelligence", "In", "the", "1950", "s", ",", "Turing", "continued", "to", "theorise", "about", "the", "potential", "of", "computers", "in", "the", "future", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 6], [7, 16], [17, 20], [21, 25], [26, 28], [29, 39], [40, 52], [53, 55], [56, 59], [60, 64], [64, 65], [65, 66], [67, 73], [74, 83], [84, 86], [87, 95], [96, 101], [102, 105], [106, 115], [116, 118], [119, 128], [129, 131], [132, 135], [136, 142], [142, 143]], "normalized_time": ["1950s"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1950s", "normalized": "1950s", "type": "decade", "offset_start": 60, "offset_end": 65}], "labels": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000110", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 110, "text": "As a result of this work, Turing is now considered to be one of the fathers of machine learning and what we now know as artificial intelligence or AI. He also devised what has become known as the ‘Turing Test’, where he proposed a game in which, by asking only written questions and studying written answers, a player had to determine whether the answers were coming from a human or a machine.", "tokens": ["As", "a", "result", "of", "this", "work", ",", "Turing", "is", "now", "considered", "to", "be", "one", "of", "the", "fathers", "of", "machine", "learning", "and", "what", "we", "now", "know", "as", "artificial", "intelligence", "or", "AI", ".", "He", "also", "devised", "what", "has", "become", "known", "as", "the", "‘", "Turing", "Test", "’", ",", "where", "he", "proposed", "a", "game", "in", "which", ",", "by", "asking", "only", "written", "questions", "and", "studying", "written", "answers", ",", "a", "player", "had", "to", "determine", "whether", "the", "answers", "were", "coming", "from", "a", "human", "or", "a", "machine", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 4], [5, 11], [12, 14], [15, 19], [20, 24], [24, 25], [26, 32], [33, 35], [36, 39], [40, 50], [51, 53], [54, 56], [57, 60], [61, 63], [64, 67], [68, 75], [76, 78], [79, 86], [87, 95], [96, 99], [100, 104], [105, 107], [108, 111], [112, 116], [117, 119], [120, 130], [131, 143], [144, 146], [147, 149], [149, 150], [151, 153], [154, 158], [159, 166], [167, 171], [172, 175], [176, 182], [183, 188], [189, 191], [192, 195], [196, 197], [197, 203], [204, 208], [208, 209], [209, 210], [211, 216], [217, 219], [220, 228], [229, 230], [231, 235], [236, 238], [239, 244], [244, 245], [246, 248], [249, 255], [256, 260], [261, 268], [269, 278], [279, 282], [283, 291], [292, 299], [300, 307], [307, 308], [309, 310], [311, 317], [318, 321], [322, 324], [325, 334], [335, 342], [343, 346], [347, 354], [355, 359], [360, 366], [367, 371], [372, 373], [374, 379], [380, 382], [383, 384], [385, 392], [392, 393]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "manual_reviewed_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked_manual_reviewed", "weak_label_confidence": 0.95, "weak_label_stage": "manual_reviewed"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000111", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 111, "text": "The question of whether a machine can, or indeed has, passed this test is widely debated today.", "tokens": ["The", "question", "of", "whether", "a", "machine", "can", ",", "or", "indeed", "has", ",", "passed", "this", "test", "is", "widely", "debated", "today", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 3], [4, 12], [13, 15], [16, 23], [24, 25], [26, 33], [34, 37], [37, 38], [39, 41], [42, 48], [49, 52], [52, 53], [54, 60], [61, 65], [66, 70], [71, 73], [74, 80], [81, 88], [89, 94], [94, 95]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000114", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 114, "text": "In the 1950s, Turing continued to theorise about the potential of computers in the future.", "tokens": ["In", "the", "1950", "s", ",", "Turing", "continued", "to", "theorise", "about", "the", "potential", "of", "computers", "in", "the", "future", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 6], [7, 11], [11, 12], [12, 13], [14, 20], [21, 30], [31, 33], [34, 42], [43, 48], [49, 52], [53, 62], [63, 65], [66, 75], [76, 78], [79, 82], [83, 89], [89, 90]], "normalized_time": ["1950s"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1950s", "normalized": "1950s", "type": "decade", "offset_start": 7, "offset_end": 12}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000128", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 128, "text": "After 1967, the law started to change, and Turing would not be prosecuted today.", "tokens": ["After", "1967", ",", "the", "law", "started", "to", "change", ",", "and", "Turing", "would", "not", "be", "prosecuted", "today", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 5], [6, 10], [10, 11], [12, 15], [16, 19], [20, 27], [28, 30], [31, 37], [37, 38], [39, 42], [43, 49], [50, 55], [56, 59], [60, 62], [63, 73], [74, 79], [79, 80]], "normalized_time": ["1967"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1967", "normalized": "1967", "type": "year", "offset_start": 6, "offset_end": 10}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000133", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 133, "text": "Alan Turing described himself to Joan Clarke at Bletchley Park as ‘having homosexual tendencies’.", "tokens": ["Alan", "Turing", "described", "himself", "to", "Joan", "Clarke", "at", "Bletchley", "Park", "as", "‘", "having", "homosexual", "tendencies", "’", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 4], [5, 11], [12, 21], [22, 29], [30, 32], [33, 37], [38, 44], [45, 47], [48, 57], [58, 62], [63, 65], [66, 67], [67, 73], [74, 84], [85, 95], [95, 96], [96, 97]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000145", "doc_id": "doc_0001", "source_id": "src_first_001", "sentence_index_in_doc": 145, "text": "Many have questioned this verdict, including Sara Turing, Alan’s mother, who believed the death was accidental and the product of an experimental mishap.", "tokens": ["Many", "have", "questioned", "this", "verdict", ",", "including", "Sara", "Turing", ",", "Alan", "’", "s", "mother", ",", "who", "believed", "the", "death", "was", "accidental", "and", "the", "product", "of", "an", "experimental", "mishap", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 4], [5, 9], [10, 20], [21, 25], [26, 33], [33, 34], [35, 44], [45, 49], [50, 56], [56, 57], [58, 62], [62, 63], [63, 64], [65, 71], [71, 72], [73, 76], [77, 85], [86, 89], [90, 95], [96, 99], [100, 110], [111, 114], [115, 118], [119, 126], [127, 129], [130, 132], [133, 145], [146, 152], [152, 153]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000176", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 22, "text": "She can add such things as “I am the woman, don’t listen to him!”", "tokens": ["She", "can", "add", "such", "things", "as", "“", "I", "am", "the", "woman", ",", "don", "’", "t", "listen", "to", "him", "!", "”"], "token_spans": [[0, 3], [4, 7], [8, 11], [12, 16], [17, 23], [24, 26], [27, 28], [28, 29], [30, 32], [33, 36], [37, 42], [42, 43], [44, 47], [47, 48], [48, 49], [50, 56], [57, 59], [60, 63], [63, 64], [64, 65]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000188", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 34, "text": "never could write poetry.", "tokens": ["never", "could", "write", "poetry", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 5], [6, 11], [12, 17], [18, 24], [24, 25]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000198", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 44, "text": "The conditions of our game make these disabilities irrelevant.", "tokens": ["The", "conditions", "of", "our", "game", "make", "these", "disabilities", "irrelevant", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 3], [4, 14], [15, 17], [18, 21], [22, 26], [27, 31], [32, 37], [38, 50], [51, 61], [61, 62]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000208", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 54, "text": "What sorts of machines can take part in the imitation game?", "tokens": ["What", "sorts", "of", "machines", "can", "take", "part", "in", "the", "imitation", "game", "?"], "token_spans": [[0, 4], [5, 10], [11, 13], [14, 22], [23, 26], [27, 31], [32, 36], [37, 39], [40, 43], [44, 53], [54, 58], [58, 59]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000245", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 91, "text": "The speed which would have been available would be definitely faster than a human computer but something like I00 times slower than the Manchester machine, itself one of the slower of the modern machines.", "tokens": ["The", "speed", "which", "would", "have", "been", "available", "would", "be", "definitely", "faster", "than", "a", "human", "computer", "but", "something", "like", "I", "00", "times", "slower", "than", "the", "Manchester", "machine", ",", "itself", "one", "of", "the", "slower", "of", "the", "modern", "machines", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 3], [4, 9], [10, 15], [16, 21], [22, 26], [27, 31], [32, 41], [42, 47], [48, 50], [51, 61], [62, 68], [69, 73], [74, 75], [76, 81], [82, 90], [91, 94], [95, 104], [105, 109], [110, 111], [111, 113], [114, 119], [120, 126], [127, 131], [132, 135], [136, 146], [147, 154], [154, 155], [156, 162], [163, 166], [167, 169], [170, 173], [174, 180], [181, 183], [184, 187], [188, 194], [195, 203], [203, 204]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000271", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 117, "text": "They can be described by such tables provided they have only a finite number of possible states.", "tokens": ["They", "can", "be", "described", "by", "such", "tables", "provided", "they", "have", "only", "a", "finite", "number", "of", "possible", "states", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 4], [5, 8], [9, 11], [12, 21], [22, 24], [25, 29], [30, 36], [37, 45], [46, 50], [51, 55], [56, 60], [61, 62], [63, 69], [70, 76], [77, 79], [80, 88], [89, 95], [95, 96]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000296", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 142, "text": "Turing now turns to objections.", "tokens": ["Turing", "now", "turns", "to", "objections", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 6], [7, 10], [11, 16], [17, 19], [20, 30], [30, 31]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000305", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 151, "text": "It may be the most logical view to hold but it makes communication of ideas difficult.", "tokens": ["It", "may", "be", "the", "most", "logical", "view", "to", "hold", "but", "it", "makes", "communication", "of", "ideas", "difficult", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 6], [7, 9], [10, 13], [14, 18], [19, 26], [27, 31], [32, 34], [35, 39], [40, 43], [44, 46], [47, 52], [53, 66], [67, 69], [70, 75], [76, 85], [85, 86]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000316", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 162, "text": "By a winter’s day one means a typical winter’s day, rather than a special one like Christmas.", "tokens": ["By", "a", "winter", "’", "s", "day", "one", "means", "a", "typical", "winter", "’", "s", "day", ",", "rather", "than", "a", "special", "one", "like", "Christmas", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 4], [5, 11], [11, 12], [12, 13], [14, 17], [18, 21], [22, 27], [28, 29], [30, 37], [38, 44], [44, 45], [45, 46], [47, 50], [50, 51], [52, 58], [59, 63], [64, 65], [66, 73], [74, 77], [78, 82], [83, 92], [92, 93]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000331", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 177, "text": "They are ugly, each is designed for a very limited purpose, when required for a minutely different purpose they are useless, the variety of behaviour of any one of them is very small, etc., etc. Naturally he concludes that these are necessary properties of machines in general.", "tokens": ["They", "are", "ugly", ",", "each", "is", "designed", "for", "a", "very", "limited", "purpose", ",", "when", "required", "for", "a", "minutely", "different", "purpose", "they", "are", "useless", ",", "the", "variety", "of", "behaviour", "of", "any", "one", "of", "them", "is", "very", "small", ",", "etc", ".", ",", "etc", ".", "Naturally", "he", "concludes", "that", "these", "are", "necessary", "properties", "of", "machines", "in", "general", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 4], [5, 8], [9, 13], [13, 14], [15, 19], [20, 22], [23, 31], [32, 35], [36, 37], [38, 42], [43, 50], [51, 58], [58, 59], [60, 64], [65, 73], [74, 77], [78, 79], [80, 88], [89, 98], [99, 106], [107, 111], [112, 115], [116, 123], [123, 124], [125, 128], [129, 136], [137, 139], [140, 149], [150, 152], [153, 156], [157, 160], [161, 163], [164, 168], [169, 171], [172, 176], [177, 182], [182, 183], [184, 187], [187, 188], [188, 189], [190, 193], [193, 194], [195, 204], [205, 207], [208, 217], [218, 222], [223, 228], [229, 232], [233, 242], [243, 253], [254, 256], [257, 265], [266, 268], [269, 276], [276, 277]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "manual_reviewed_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked_manual_reviewed", "weak_label_confidence": 0.95, "weak_label_stage": "manual_reviewed"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000334", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 180, "text": "The exact definition does not matter as no mathematical accuracy is claimed in the present discussion.)", "tokens": ["The", "exact", "definition", "does", "not", "matter", "as", "no", "mathematical", "accuracy", "is", "claimed", "in", "the", "present", "discussion", ".", ")"], "token_spans": [[0, 3], [4, 9], [10, 20], [21, 25], [26, 29], [30, 36], [37, 39], [40, 42], [43, 55], [56, 64], [65, 67], [68, 75], [76, 78], [79, 82], [83, 90], [91, 101], [101, 102], [102, 103]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000348", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 194, "text": "It is claimed that the interrogator could distinguish the machine from the man simply by setting them a number of problems in arithmetic.", "tokens": ["It", "is", "claimed", "that", "the", "interrogator", "could", "distinguish", "the", "machine", "from", "the", "man", "simply", "by", "setting", "them", "a", "number", "of", "problems", "in", "arithmetic", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 5], [6, 13], [14, 18], [19, 22], [23, 35], [36, 41], [42, 53], [54, 57], [58, 65], [66, 70], [71, 74], [75, 78], [79, 85], [86, 88], [89, 96], [97, 101], [102, 103], [104, 110], [111, 113], [114, 122], [123, 125], [126, 136], [136, 137]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000350", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 196, "text": "The reply to this is simple.", "tokens": ["The", "reply", "to", "this", "is", "simple", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 3], [4, 9], [10, 12], [13, 17], [18, 20], [21, 27], [27, 28]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000354", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 200, "text": "Even this interpretation of the criticism is not sufficiently sympathetic.", "tokens": ["Even", "this", "interpretation", "of", "the", "criticism", "is", "not", "sufficiently", "sympathetic", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 4], [5, 9], [10, 24], [25, 27], [28, 31], [32, 41], [42, 44], [45, 48], [49, 61], [62, 73], [73, 74]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000359", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 205, "text": "one is therefore discussing “abstract machines.”", "tokens": ["one", "is", "therefore", "discussing", "“", "abstract", "machines", ".", "”"], "token_spans": [[0, 3], [4, 6], [7, 16], [17, 27], [28, 29], [29, 37], [38, 46], [46, 47], [47, 48]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000360", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 206, "text": "These abstract machines are mathematical fictions rather than physical objects.", "tokens": ["These", "abstract", "machines", "are", "mathematical", "fictions", "rather", "than", "physical", "objects", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 5], [6, 14], [15, 23], [24, 27], [28, 40], [41, 49], [50, 56], [57, 61], [62, 70], [71, 78], [78, 79]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000367", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 213, "text": "It might do nothing but type out repeatedly “O = I.” To take a less", "tokens": ["It", "might", "do", "nothing", "but", "type", "out", "repeatedly", "“", "O", "=", "I", ".", "”", "To", "take", "a", "less"], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 8], [9, 11], [12, 19], [20, 23], [24, 28], [29, 32], [33, 43], [44, 45], [45, 46], [47, 48], [49, 50], [50, 51], [51, 52], [53, 55], [56, 60], [61, 62], [63, 67]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000371", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 217, "text": "A small error in the information about the size of a nervous impulse impinging on a neuron, may make a large difference to the size of the outgoing impulse.", "tokens": ["A", "small", "error", "in", "the", "information", "about", "the", "size", "of", "a", "nervous", "impulse", "impinging", "on", "a", "neuron", ",", "may", "make", "a", "large", "difference", "to", "the", "size", "of", "the", "outgoing", "impulse", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 1], [2, 7], [8, 13], [14, 16], [17, 20], [21, 32], [33, 38], [39, 42], [43, 47], [48, 50], [51, 52], [53, 60], [61, 68], [69, 78], [79, 81], [82, 83], [84, 90], [90, 91], [92, 95], [96, 100], [101, 102], [103, 108], [109, 119], [120, 122], [123, 126], [127, 131], [132, 134], [135, 138], [139, 147], [148, 155], [155, 156]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000377", "doc_id": "doc_0002", "source_id": "src_first_002", "sentence_index_in_doc": 223, "text": "(A differential analyser is a certain kind of machine not of the discrete-state type used for some kinds of calculation.)", "tokens": ["(", "A", "differential", "analyser", "is", "a", "certain", "kind", "of", "machine", "not", "of", "the", "discrete-state", "type", "used", "for", "some", "kinds", "of", "calculation", ".", ")"], "token_spans": [[0, 1], [1, 2], [3, 15], [16, 24], [25, 27], [28, 29], [30, 37], [38, 42], [43, 45], [46, 53], [54, 57], [58, 60], [61, 64], [65, 79], [80, 84], [85, 89], [90, 93], [94, 98], [99, 104], [105, 107], [108, 119], [119, 120], [120, 121]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000390", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 1, "text": "Alan Mathison Turing (1912-54) On this page Childhood Cambridge The Entscheidungsproblem Princeton and Bletchley Park After the War and Artificial Intelligence Morphogenesis The Final Years Acknowledgements This is an exhibition about Alan Turing illustrated with documents from papers held at the Archive Centre.", "tokens": ["Alan", "Mathison", "Turing", "(", "1912", "-", "54", ")", "On", "this", "page", "Childhood", "Cambridge", "The", "Entscheidungsproblem", "Princeton", "and", "Bletchley", "Park", "After", "the", "War", "and", "Artificial", "Intelligence", "Morphogenesis", "The", "Final", "Years", "Acknowledgements", "This", "is", "an", "exhibition", "about", "Alan", "Turing", "illustrated", "with", "documents", "from", "papers", "held", "at", "the", "Archive", "Centre", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 4], [5, 13], [14, 20], [21, 22], [22, 26], [26, 27], [27, 29], [29, 30], [31, 33], [34, 38], [39, 43], [44, 53], [54, 63], [64, 67], [68, 88], [89, 98], [99, 102], [103, 112], [113, 117], [118, 123], [124, 127], [128, 131], [132, 135], [136, 146], [147, 159], [160, 173], [174, 177], [178, 183], [184, 189], [190, 206], [207, 211], [212, 214], [215, 217], [218, 228], [229, 234], [235, 239], [240, 246], [247, 258], [259, 263], [264, 273], [274, 278], [279, 285], [286, 290], [291, 293], [294, 297], [298, 305], [306, 312], [312, 313]], "normalized_time": ["1912-1954"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1912-54", "normalized": "1912-1954", "type": "year_range", "offset_start": 22, "offset_end": 29}], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "B-CONCEPT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000394", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 5, "text": "Alan (the younger of the two) attended Hazelhurst preparatory school 1922-6.", "tokens": ["Alan", "(", "the", "younger", "of", "the", "two", ")", "attended", "Hazelhurst", "preparatory", "school", "1922", "-", "6", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 4], [5, 6], [6, 9], [10, 17], [18, 20], [21, 24], [25, 28], [28, 29], [30, 38], [39, 49], [50, 61], [62, 68], [69, 73], [73, 74], [74, 75], [75, 76]], "normalized_time": ["1922"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1922", "normalized": "1922", "type": "year", "offset_start": 69, "offset_end": 73}], "labels": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000409", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 20, "text": "Princeton and Bletchley Park The completion of his research into Hilbert’s Entscheidungsproblem in 1936 coincided with the decision to study at Princeton University with Alonzo Church.", "tokens": ["Princeton", "and", "Bletchley", "Park", "The", "completion", "of", "his", "research", "into", "Hilbert", "’", "s", "Entscheidungsproblem", "in", "1936", "coincided", "with", "the", "decision", "to", "study", "at", "Princeton", "University", "with", "Alonzo", "Church", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 9], [10, 13], [14, 23], [24, 28], [29, 32], [33, 43], [44, 46], [47, 50], [51, 59], [60, 64], [65, 72], [72, 73], [73, 74], [75, 95], [96, 98], [99, 103], [104, 113], [114, 118], [119, 122], [123, 131], [132, 134], [135, 140], [141, 143], [144, 153], [154, 164], [165, 169], [170, 176], [177, 183], [183, 184]], "normalized_time": ["1936"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1936", "normalized": "1936", "type": "year", "offset_start": 99, "offset_end": 103}], "labels": ["B-LOC", "O", "B-LOC", "I-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "B-CONCEPT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000415", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 26, "text": "He did not sell his idea to ‘H.M. Government for quite a substantial sum’ as mentioned in the letter.", "tokens": ["He", "did", "not", "sell", "his", "idea", "to", "‘", "H", ".", "M", ".", "Government", "for", "quite", "a", "substantial", "sum", "’", "as", "mentioned", "in", "the", "letter", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 6], [7, 10], [11, 15], [16, 19], [20, 24], [25, 27], [28, 29], [29, 30], [30, 31], [31, 32], [32, 33], [34, 44], [45, 48], [49, 54], [55, 56], [57, 68], [69, 72], [72, 73], [74, 76], [77, 86], [87, 89], [90, 93], [94, 100], [100, 101]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000417", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 28, "text": "He developed electronic technology to increase the speed of the mechanical operations that were performed thousands of times every day in decoding intercepted German messages.", "tokens": ["He", "developed", "electronic", "technology", "to", "increase", "the", "speed", "of", "the", "mechanical", "operations", "that", "were", "performed", "thousands", "of", "times", "every", "day", "in", "decoding", "intercepted", "German", "messages", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 12], [13, 23], [24, 34], [35, 37], [38, 46], [47, 50], [51, 56], [57, 59], [60, 63], [64, 74], [75, 85], [86, 90], [91, 95], [96, 105], [106, 115], [116, 118], [119, 124], [125, 130], [131, 134], [135, 137], [138, 146], [147, 158], [159, 165], [166, 174], [174, 175]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000428", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 39, "text": "In the late 1940s and 1950s he continued to research, write and broadcast on the emerging discipline of computing.", "tokens": ["In", "the", "late", "1940", "s", "and", "1950", "s", "he", "continued", "to", "research", ",", "write", "and", "broadcast", "on", "the", "emerging", "discipline", "of", "computing", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 6], [7, 11], [12, 16], [16, 17], [18, 21], [22, 26], [26, 27], [28, 30], [31, 40], [41, 43], [44, 52], [52, 53], [54, 59], [60, 63], [64, 73], [74, 76], [77, 80], [81, 89], [90, 100], [101, 103], [104, 113], [113, 114]], "normalized_time": ["1940s", "1950s"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1940s", "normalized": "1940s", "type": "decade", "offset_start": 12, "offset_end": 17}, {"text": "1950s", "normalized": "1950s", "type": "decade", "offset_start": 22, "offset_end": 27}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000433", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 44, "text": "Turing continued to supervise students at King's.", "tokens": ["Turing", "continued", "to", "supervise", "students", "at", "King's", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 6], [7, 16], [17, 19], [20, 29], [30, 38], [39, 41], [42, 48], [48, 49]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000448", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 59, "text": "King’s College is also grateful to the Turing family, the Turing Trust, Prof. I.J. Good, Dr. Andrew Hodges, N.E. Hoskin, Prof. C.B. Jones, Dr. Norman Routledge, Prof. M.V. Wilkes, and Prof. Mike Yates for their generosity in providing documents and advice.", "tokens": ["King", "’", "s", "College", "is", "also", "grateful", "to", "the", "Turing", "family", ",", "the", "Turing", "Trust", ",", "Prof", ".", "I", ".", "J", ".", "Good", ",", "Dr", ".", "Andrew", "Hodges", ",", "N", ".", "E", ".", "Hoskin", ",", "Prof", ".", "C", ".", "B", ".", "Jones", ",", "Dr", ".", "Norman", "Routledge", ",", "Prof", ".", "M", ".", "V", ".", "Wilkes", ",", "and", "Prof", ".", "Mike", "Yates", "for", "their", "generosity", "in", "providing", "documents", "and", "advice", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 4], [4, 5], [5, 6], [7, 14], [15, 17], [18, 22], [23, 31], [32, 34], [35, 38], [39, 45], [46, 52], [52, 53], [54, 57], [58, 64], [65, 70], [70, 71], [72, 76], [76, 77], [78, 79], [79, 80], [80, 81], [81, 82], [83, 87], [87, 88], [89, 91], [91, 92], [93, 99], [100, 106], [106, 107], [108, 109], [109, 110], [110, 111], [111, 112], [113, 119], [119, 120], [121, 125], [125, 126], [127, 128], [128, 129], [129, 130], [130, 131], [132, 137], [137, 138], [139, 141], [141, 142], [143, 149], [150, 159], [159, 160], [161, 165], [165, 166], [167, 168], [168, 169], [169, 170], [170, 171], [172, 178], [178, 179], [180, 183], [184, 188], [188, 189], [190, 194], [195, 200], [201, 204], [205, 210], [211, 221], [222, 224], [225, 234], [235, 244], [245, 248], [249, 255], [255, 256]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "manual_reviewed_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked_manual_reviewed", "weak_label_confidence": 0.95, "weak_label_stage": "manual_reviewed"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000469", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 80, "text": "These concluded with an outline of David Hilbert’s call for an answer to the question ‘Was mathematics decidable’?", "tokens": ["These", "concluded", "with", "an", "outline", "of", "David", "Hilbert", "’", "s", "call", "for", "an", "answer", "to", "the", "question", "‘", "Was", "mathematics", "decidable", "’", "?"], "token_spans": [[0, 5], [6, 15], [16, 20], [21, 23], [24, 31], [32, 34], [35, 40], [41, 48], [48, 49], [49, 50], [51, 55], [56, 59], [60, 62], [63, 69], [70, 72], [73, 76], [77, 85], [86, 87], [87, 90], [91, 102], [103, 112], [112, 113], [113, 114]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000472", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 83, "text": "and into 1936 Turing worked on his proof with Newman’s guidance.", "tokens": ["and", "into", "1936", "Turing", "worked", "on", "his", "proof", "with", "Newman", "’", "s", "guidance", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 3], [4, 8], [9, 13], [14, 20], [21, 27], [28, 30], [31, 34], [35, 40], [41, 45], [46, 52], [52, 53], [53, 54], [55, 63], [63, 64]], "normalized_time": ["1936"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1936", "normalized": "1936", "type": "year", "offset_start": 9, "offset_end": 13}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000479", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 90, "text": "coincided with the decision to study at Princeton University with.", "tokens": ["coincided", "with", "the", "decision", "to", "study", "at", "Princeton", "University", "with", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 9], [10, 14], [15, 18], [19, 27], [28, 30], [31, 36], [37, 39], [40, 49], [50, 60], [61, 65], [65, 66]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000484", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 95, "text": "He wrote to his mother (see letter dated 6 October 1936, below) about his trials and tribulations in travel.", "tokens": ["He", "wrote", "to", "his", "mother", "(", "see", "letter", "dated", "6", "October", "1936", ",", "below", ")", "about", "his", "trials", "and", "tribulations", "in", "travel", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 8], [9, 11], [12, 15], [16, 22], [23, 24], [24, 27], [28, 34], [35, 40], [41, 42], [43, 50], [51, 55], [55, 56], [57, 62], [62, 63], [64, 69], [70, 73], [74, 80], [81, 84], [85, 97], [98, 100], [101, 107], [107, 108]], "normalized_time": ["1936-10-06"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "6 October 1936", "normalized": "1936-10-06", "type": "date", "offset_start": 41, "offset_end": 55}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000495", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 106, "text": "After the War and Artificial Intelligence.", "tokens": ["After", "the", "War", "and", "Artificial", "Intelligence", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 5], [6, 9], [10, 13], [14, 17], [18, 28], [29, 41], [41, 42]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000502", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 113, "text": "He continued also to work on mathematical logic, in particular the theory of types.", "tokens": ["He", "continued", "also", "to", "work", "on", "mathematical", "logic", ",", "in", "particular", "the", "theory", "of", "types", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 12], [13, 17], [18, 20], [21, 25], [26, 28], [29, 41], [42, 47], [47, 48], [49, 51], [52, 62], [63, 66], [67, 73], [74, 76], [77, 82], [82, 83]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000510", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 121, "text": "In 1952 his paper on morphogenetic theory was published in the Proceedings of the Royal Society.", "tokens": ["In", "1952", "his", "paper", "on", "morphogenetic", "theory", "was", "published", "in", "the", "Proceedings", "of", "the", "Royal", "Society", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 7], [8, 11], [12, 17], [18, 20], [21, 34], [35, 41], [42, 45], [46, 55], [56, 58], [59, 62], [63, 74], [75, 77], [78, 81], [82, 87], [88, 95], [95, 96]], "normalized_time": ["1952"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1952", "normalized": "1952", "type": "year", "offset_start": 3, "offset_end": 7}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000522", "doc_id": "doc_0003", "source_id": "src_first_003", "sentence_index_in_doc": 133, "text": "The papers of Alan Turing have been assembled in the Archive Centre at King’s College, Cambridge from a number of sources since 1960 when his mother, Sara Turing, made the first presentation.", "tokens": ["The", "papers", "of", "Alan", "Turing", "have", "been", "assembled", "in", "the", "Archive", "Centre", "at", "King", "’", "s", "College", ",", "Cambridge", "from", "a", "number", "of", "sources", "since", "1960", "when", "his", "mother", ",", "Sara", "Turing", ",", "made", "the", "first", "presentation", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 3], [4, 10], [11, 13], [14, 18], [19, 25], [26, 30], [31, 35], [36, 45], [46, 48], [49, 52], [53, 60], [61, 67], [68, 70], [71, 75], [75, 76], [76, 77], [78, 85], [85, 86], [87, 96], [97, 101], [102, 103], [104, 110], [111, 113], [114, 121], [122, 127], [128, 132], [133, 137], [138, 141], [142, 148], [148, 149], [150, 154], [155, 161], [161, 162], [163, 167], [168, 171], [172, 177], [178, 190], [190, 191]], "normalized_time": ["1960"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1960", "normalized": "1960", "type": "year", "offset_start": 128, "offset_end": 132}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000531", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 5, "text": "Transformational Impact Alan Mathison Turing, considered by many to be the “father of computer science,” earned his Princeton Ph.D. in mathematics.", "tokens": ["Transformational", "Impact", "Alan", "Mathison", "Turing", ",", "considered", "by", "many", "to", "be", "the", "“", "father", "of", "computer", "science", ",", "”", "earned", "his", "Princeton", "Ph", ".", "D", ".", "in", "mathematics", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 16], [17, 23], [24, 28], [29, 37], [38, 44], [44, 45], [46, 56], [57, 59], [60, 64], [65, 67], [68, 70], [71, 74], [75, 76], [76, 82], [83, 85], [86, 94], [95, 102], [102, 103], [103, 104], [105, 111], [112, 115], [116, 125], [126, 128], [128, 129], [129, 130], [130, 131], [132, 134], [135, 146], [146, 147]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000532", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 6, "text": "In January 2008, the Princeton Alumni Weekly (PAW) published a list of the top 25 most influential Princeton alumni Link is external.", "tokens": ["In", "January", "2008", ",", "the", "Princeton", "Alumni", "Weekly", "(", "PAW", ")", "published", "a", "list", "of", "the", "top", "25", "most", "influential", "Princeton", "alumni", "Link", "is", "external", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 10], [11, 15], [15, 16], [17, 20], [21, 30], [31, 37], [38, 44], [45, 46], [46, 49], [49, 50], [51, 60], [61, 62], [63, 67], [68, 70], [71, 74], [75, 78], [79, 81], [82, 86], [87, 98], [99, 108], [109, 115], [116, 120], [121, 123], [124, 132], [132, 133]], "normalized_time": ["2008-01"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "January 2008", "normalized": "2008-01", "type": "month_year", "offset_start": 3, "offset_end": 15}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "O", "B-WORK", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000535", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 9, "text": "A pioneer in computational science When Turing came to the Princeton Graduate School in 1936 after studies at King's College, Cambridge, he had already written the seminal paper, \"On Computable Numbers.\"", "tokens": ["A", "pioneer", "in", "computational", "science", "When", "Turing", "came", "to", "the", "Princeton", "Graduate", "School", "in", "1936", "after", "studies", "at", "King's", "College", ",", "Cambridge", ",", "he", "had", "already", "written", "the", "seminal", "paper", ",", "\"", "On", "Computable", "Numbers", ".", "\""], "token_spans": [[0, 1], [2, 9], [10, 12], [13, 26], [27, 34], [35, 39], [40, 46], [47, 51], [52, 54], [55, 58], [59, 68], [69, 77], [78, 84], [85, 87], [88, 92], [93, 98], [99, 106], [107, 109], [110, 116], [117, 124], [124, 125], [126, 135], [135, 136], [137, 139], [140, 143], [144, 151], [152, 159], [160, 163], [164, 171], [172, 177], [177, 178], [179, 180], [180, 182], [183, 193], [194, 201], [201, 202], [202, 203]], "normalized_time": ["1936"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1936", "normalized": "1936", "type": "year", "offset_start": 88, "offset_end": 92}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000536", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 10, "text": "In that paper, Turing described simple abstract computational devices that his Princeton adviser Alonzo Church'24 *27 — the renowned mathematician, logician, and philosopher — later coined as “Turing machines.”", "tokens": ["In", "that", "paper", ",", "Turing", "described", "simple", "abstract", "computational", "devices", "that", "his", "Princeton", "adviser", "Alonzo", "Church", "'", "24", "*", "27", "—", "the", "renowned", "mathematician", ",", "logician", ",", "and", "philosopher", "—", "later", "coined", "as", "“", "Turing", "machines", ".", "”"], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 7], [8, 13], [13, 14], [15, 21], [22, 31], [32, 38], [39, 47], [48, 61], [62, 69], [70, 74], [75, 78], [79, 88], [89, 96], [97, 103], [104, 110], [110, 111], [111, 113], [114, 115], [115, 117], [118, 119], [120, 123], [124, 132], [133, 146], [146, 147], [148, 156], [156, 157], [158, 161], [162, 173], [174, 175], [176, 181], [182, 188], [189, 191], [192, 193], [193, 199], [200, 208], [208, 209], [209, 210]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "O", "O"], "label_source": "manual_reviewed_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked_manual_reviewed", "weak_label_confidence": 0.95, "weak_label_stage": "manual_reviewed"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000538", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 12, "text": "(See Andrew Appel's “The Birth of Computer Science at Princeton in the 1930s Link downloads document.”)", "tokens": ["(", "See", "Andrew", "Appel's", "“", "The", "Birth", "of", "Computer", "Science", "at", "Princeton", "in", "the", "1930", "s", "Link", "downloads", "document", ".", "”", ")"], "token_spans": [[0, 1], [1, 4], [5, 11], [12, 19], [20, 21], [21, 24], [25, 30], [31, 33], [34, 42], [43, 50], [51, 53], [54, 63], [64, 66], [67, 70], [71, 75], [75, 76], [77, 81], [82, 91], [92, 100], [100, 101], [101, 102], [102, 103]], "normalized_time": ["1930s"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1930s", "normalized": "1930s", "type": "decade", "offset_start": 71, "offset_end": 76}], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000543", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 17, "text": "In this 2012 video, Appel discusses Turing's legacy.", "tokens": ["In", "this", "2012", "video", ",", "Appel", "discusses", "Turing's", "legacy", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 7], [8, 12], [13, 18], [18, 19], [20, 25], [26, 35], [36, 44], [45, 51], [51, 52]], "normalized_time": ["2012"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "2012", "normalized": "2012", "type": "year", "offset_start": 8, "offset_end": 12}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000547", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 21, "text": "In 2013, the British government granted Turing a posthumous pardon, following an apology for “the appalling way he was treated,” and now upholds an amnesty law informally known as the Alan Turing law.", "tokens": ["In", "2013", ",", "the", "British", "government", "granted", "Turing", "a", "posthumous", "pardon", ",", "following", "an", "apology", "for", "“", "the", "appalling", "way", "he", "was", "treated", ",", "”", "and", "now", "upholds", "an", "amnesty", "law", "informally", "known", "as", "the", "Alan", "Turing", "law", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 7], [7, 8], [9, 12], [13, 20], [21, 31], [32, 39], [40, 46], [47, 48], [49, 59], [60, 66], [66, 67], [68, 77], [78, 80], [81, 88], [89, 92], [93, 94], [94, 97], [98, 107], [108, 111], [112, 114], [115, 118], [119, 126], [126, 127], [127, 128], [129, 132], [133, 136], [137, 144], [145, 147], [148, 155], [156, 159], [160, 170], [171, 176], [177, 179], [180, 183], [184, 188], [189, 195], [196, 199], [199, 200]], "normalized_time": ["2013"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "2013", "normalized": "2013", "type": "year", "offset_start": 3, "offset_end": 7}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O"], "label_source": "manual_reviewed_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked_manual_reviewed", "weak_label_confidence": 0.95, "weak_label_stage": "manual_reviewed"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000550", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 24, "text": "Rexford'91 was chair of the computer science department at the time and became provost of Princeton in 2023.", "tokens": ["Rexford", "'", "91", "was", "chair", "of", "the", "computer", "science", "department", "at", "the", "time", "and", "became", "provost", "of", "Princeton", "in", "2023", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 7], [7, 8], [8, 10], [11, 14], [15, 20], [21, 23], [24, 27], [28, 36], [37, 44], [45, 55], [56, 58], [59, 62], [63, 67], [68, 71], [72, 78], [79, 86], [87, 89], [90, 99], [100, 102], [103, 107], [107, 108]], "normalized_time": ["2023"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "2023", "normalized": "2023", "type": "year", "offset_start": 103, "offset_end": 107}], "labels": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000553", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 27, "text": "“For those of us in the LGBTQ community, Turing is an enduring icon, and the growing appreciation of his life and his great contributions to the world are a cause for hope and celebration,” she added.", "tokens": ["“", "For", "those", "of", "us", "in", "the", "LGBTQ", "community", ",", "Turing", "is", "an", "enduring", "icon", ",", "and", "the", "growing", "appreciation", "of", "his", "life", "and", "his", "great", "contributions", "to", "the", "world", "are", "a", "cause", "for", "hope", "and", "celebration", ",", "”", "she", "added", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 1], [1, 4], [5, 10], [11, 13], [14, 16], [17, 19], [20, 23], [24, 29], [30, 39], [39, 40], [41, 47], [48, 50], [51, 53], [54, 62], [63, 67], [67, 68], [69, 72], [73, 76], [77, 84], [85, 97], [98, 100], [101, 104], [105, 109], [110, 113], [114, 117], [118, 123], [124, 137], [138, 140], [141, 144], [145, 150], [151, 154], [155, 156], [157, 162], [163, 166], [167, 171], [172, 175], [176, 187], [187, 188], [188, 189], [190, 193], [194, 199], [199, 200]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000577", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 51, "text": "Alan Mathison Turing, considered by many to be the “father of computer science,” earned his Princeton Ph.D. in mathematics.", "tokens": ["Alan", "Mathison", "Turing", ",", "considered", "by", "many", "to", "be", "the", "“", "father", "of", "computer", "science", ",", "”", "earned", "his", "Princeton", "Ph", ".", "D", ".", "in", "mathematics", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 4], [5, 13], [14, 20], [20, 21], [22, 32], [33, 35], [36, 40], [41, 43], [44, 46], [47, 50], [51, 52], [52, 58], [59, 61], [62, 70], [71, 78], [78, 79], [79, 80], [81, 87], [88, 91], [92, 101], [102, 104], [104, 105], [105, 106], [106, 107], [108, 110], [111, 122], [122, 123]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["B-PER", "I-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "manual_reviewed_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked_manual_reviewed", "weak_label_confidence": 0.95, "weak_label_stage": "manual_reviewed"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000583", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 57, "text": "Turing came to the Princeton Graduate School in 1936 after studies at.", "tokens": ["Turing", "came", "to", "the", "Princeton", "Graduate", "School", "in", "1936", "after", "studies", "at", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 6], [7, 11], [12, 14], [15, 18], [19, 28], [29, 37], [38, 44], [45, 47], [48, 52], [53, 58], [59, 66], [67, 69], [69, 70]], "normalized_time": ["1936"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1936", "normalized": "1936", "type": "year", "offset_start": 48, "offset_end": 52}], "labels": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "I-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000584", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 58, "text": "King's College, Cambridge, he had already written the seminal paper,\"On.", "tokens": ["King's", "College", ",", "Cambridge", ",", "he", "had", "already", "written", "the", "seminal", "paper", ",", "\"", "On", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 6], [7, 14], [14, 15], [16, 25], [25, 26], [27, 29], [30, 33], [34, 41], [42, 49], [50, 53], [54, 61], [62, 67], [67, 68], [68, 69], [69, 71], [71, 72]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["B-ORG", "I-ORG", "O", "B-LOC", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000587", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 61, "text": "Church and Turing were among several.", "tokens": ["Church", "and", "Turing", "were", "among", "several", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 6], [7, 10], [11, 17], [18, 22], [23, 28], [29, 36], [36, 37]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["B-PER", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000590", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 64, "text": "(See Andrew Appel's “The Birth of Computer Science at Princeton in the 1930s Link downloads document.”)", "tokens": ["(", "See", "Andrew", "Appel's", "“", "The", "Birth", "of", "Computer", "Science", "at", "Princeton", "in", "the", "1930", "s", "Link", "downloads", "document", ".", "”", ")"], "token_spans": [[0, 1], [1, 4], [5, 11], [12, 19], [20, 21], [21, 24], [25, 30], [31, 33], [34, 42], [43, 50], [51, 53], [54, 63], [64, 66], [67, 70], [71, 75], [75, 76], [77, 81], [82, 91], [92, 100], [100, 101], [101, 102], [102, 103]], "normalized_time": ["1930s"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1930s", "normalized": "1930s", "type": "decade", "offset_start": 71, "offset_end": 76}], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "B-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "I-WORK", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "manual_reviewed_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked_manual_reviewed", "weak_label_confidence": 0.95, "weak_label_stage": "manual_reviewed"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000593", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 67, "text": "Featured speakers included Eric Schmidt, a 1976 Princeton alumnus who was Google executive chairman at the time, and eight winners of the Turing Award, often considered the computer science equivalent of the Nobel Prize.", "tokens": ["Featured", "speakers", "included", "Eric", "Schmidt", ",", "a", "1976", "Princeton", "alumnus", "who", "was", "Google", "executive", "chairman", "at", "the", "time", ",", "and", "eight", "winners", "of", "the", "Turing", "Award", ",", "often", "considered", "the", "computer", "science", "equivalent", "of", "the", "Nobel", "Prize", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 8], [9, 17], [18, 26], [27, 31], [32, 39], [39, 40], [41, 42], [43, 47], [48, 57], [58, 65], [66, 69], [70, 73], [74, 80], [81, 90], [91, 99], [100, 102], [103, 106], [107, 111], [111, 112], [113, 116], [117, 122], [123, 130], [131, 133], [134, 137], [138, 144], [145, 150], [150, 151], [152, 157], [158, 168], [169, 172], [173, 181], [182, 189], [190, 200], [201, 203], [204, 207], [208, 213], [214, 219], [219, 220]], "normalized_time": ["1976"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "1976", "normalized": "1976", "type": "year", "offset_start": 43, "offset_end": 47}], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-AWARD", "I-AWARD", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-AWARD", "I-AWARD", "O"], "label_source": "manual_reviewed_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked_manual_reviewed", "weak_label_confidence": 0.95, "weak_label_stage": "manual_reviewed"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000603", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 77, "text": "Rexford'91 was chair of the computer science department at the time and became provost of Princeton in 2023.", "tokens": ["Rexford", "'", "91", "was", "chair", "of", "the", "computer", "science", "department", "at", "the", "time", "and", "became", "provost", "of", "Princeton", "in", "2023", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 7], [7, 8], [8, 10], [11, 14], [15, 20], [21, 23], [24, 27], [28, 36], [37, 44], [45, 55], [56, 58], [59, 62], [63, 67], [68, 71], [72, 78], [79, 86], [87, 89], [90, 99], [100, 102], [103, 107], [107, 108]], "normalized_time": ["2023"], "time_mentions": [{"text": "2023", "normalized": "2023", "type": "year", "offset_start": 103, "offset_end": 107}], "labels": ["B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000606", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 80, "text": "“For those of us in the LGBTQ community, Turing is an enduring icon, and the growing appreciation of his life and his great contributions to the world are a cause for hope and celebration,” she added.", "tokens": ["“", "For", "those", "of", "us", "in", "the", "LGBTQ", "community", ",", "Turing", "is", "an", "enduring", "icon", ",", "and", "the", "growing", "appreciation", "of", "his", "life", "and", "his", "great", "contributions", "to", "the", "world", "are", "a", "cause", "for", "hope", "and", "celebration", ",", "”", "she", "added", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 1], [1, 4], [5, 10], [11, 13], [14, 16], [17, 19], [20, 23], [24, 29], [30, 39], [39, 40], [41, 47], [48, 50], [51, 53], [54, 62], [63, 67], [67, 68], [69, 72], [73, 76], [77, 84], [85, 97], [98, 100], [101, 104], [105, 109], [110, 113], [114, 117], [118, 123], [124, 137], [138, 140], [141, 144], [145, 150], [151, 154], [155, 156], [157, 162], [163, 166], [167, 171], [172, 175], [176, 187], [187, 188], [188, 189], [190, 193], [194, 199], [199, 200]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000608", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 82, "text": "In the computer science department at Princeton, we owe a tremendous intellectual debt to Alan Turing for our historical strength in theoretical computer science, of course, but also research in artificial intelligence and machine learning, and even working at the intersection of computing with biology, a topic Turing pursued in the last few years of his short life.", "tokens": ["In", "the", "computer", "science", "department", "at", "Princeton", ",", "we", "owe", "a", "tremendous", "intellectual", "debt", "to", "Alan", "Turing", "for", "our", "historical", "strength", "in", "theoretical", "computer", "science", ",", "of", "course", ",", "but", "also", "research", "in", "artificial", "intelligence", "and", "machine", "learning", ",", "and", "even", "working", "at", "the", "intersection", "of", "computing", "with", "biology", ",", "a", "topic", "Turing", "pursued", "in", "the", "last", "few", "years", "of", "his", "short", "life", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 2], [3, 6], [7, 15], [16, 23], [24, 34], [35, 37], [38, 47], [47, 48], [49, 51], [52, 55], [56, 57], [58, 68], [69, 81], [82, 86], [87, 89], [90, 94], [95, 101], [102, 105], [106, 109], [110, 120], [121, 129], [130, 132], [133, 144], [145, 153], [154, 161], [161, 162], [163, 165], [166, 172], [172, 173], [174, 177], [178, 182], [183, 191], [192, 194], [195, 205], [206, 218], [219, 222], [223, 230], [231, 239], [239, 240], [241, 244], [245, 249], [250, 257], [258, 260], [261, 264], [265, 277], [278, 280], [281, 290], [291, 295], [296, 303], [303, 304], [305, 306], [307, 312], [313, 319], [320, 327], [328, 330], [331, 334], [335, 339], [340, 343], [344, 349], [350, 352], [353, 356], [357, 362], [363, 367], [367, 368]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-ORG", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "I-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "O", "B-CONCEPT", "I-CONCEPT", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-PER", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "manual_reviewed_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked_manual_reviewed", "weak_label_confidence": 0.95, "weak_label_stage": "manual_reviewed"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000611", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 85, "text": "Legacy Highlights Pioneer in theoretical computer science WWII Codebreaker Icon of LGBTQ+ history.", "tokens": ["Legacy", "Highlights", "Pioneer", "in", "theoretical", "computer", "science", "WWII", "Codebreaker", "Icon", "of", "LGBTQ", "+", "history", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 6], [7, 17], [18, 25], [26, 28], [29, 40], [41, 49], [50, 57], [58, 62], [63, 74], [75, 79], [80, 82], [83, 88], [88, 89], [90, 97], [97, 98]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000616", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 90, "text": "Mathematical expert in the classroom and the boardroom.", "tokens": ["Mathematical", "expert", "in", "the", "classroom", "and", "the", "boardroom", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 12], [13, 19], [20, 22], [23, 26], [27, 36], [37, 40], [41, 44], [45, 54], [54, 55]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
{"sentence_id": "sent_000622", "doc_id": "doc_0004", "source_id": "src_first_004", "sentence_index_in_doc": 96, "text": "Political scientist who led higher education institutions through financial hardship.", "tokens": ["Political", "scientist", "who", "led", "higher", "education", "institutions", "through", "financial", "hardship", "."], "token_spans": [[0, 9], [10, 19], [20, 23], [24, 27], [28, 34], [35, 44], [45, 57], [58, 65], [66, 75], [76, 84], [84, 85]], "normalized_time": [], "time_mentions": [], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"], "label_source": "llm_weak_supervision", "review_status": "auto_checked", "weak_label_confidence": 0.92, "weak_label_stage": "auto_checked"}
